# Lu (Della) Wang

11413 Rockyvalley Drive NW • Calgary, Alberta • T3G5N2 CELL (519) 702-3101 • E-MAIL dellawlulu@hotmail.ca

**PROFILE** 

Business Management and Organizational Studies (BMOS) Undergraduate student at Western Ontario University with Richard Ivey School of Business Advance Entry Opportunity (AEO) status. Compassionate and dedicated with relevant experience and knowledge in in marketing, retailing, public speaking and management. Proven excellence in leadership and team working skills.

**EDUCATION** University of Western Ontario

London, ON

Business Management and Organizational studies

2014- present

- Western University Scholars student with 98% entrance average
- Advance Entry Opportunity (AEO) for Richard Ivey school of Business

## **Western Canada High School**

Calgary, AB

High school Diploma with IB certificate in Bio and Math 2011-2014

- International Baccalaureate certificate (score: 7,6)
- Life time Honour's Society member

SKILLS

- -Proficient in English
- -Proficient in Computer Skills such as MS Windows, MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, and Internet Explorer.

EXPERIENCE

Aritzia (Chinook centre & Market Mall)

2012-present

Worked as a Seasonal Sales associate for 3 consecutive years.

- Responsible for tracking shipment, sales, closing the store, and maintaining positive customer relations
- Received excellent appraisal from store manager for diligence, enthusiasm and marketing skills, with an offer of a full time position

Payless Shoesource (The Core)

Feb 2014 - Aug 2014

Worked as a part time sales associate and sales leader.

- Responsible for executing training for new employees, opening and closing, handling cash and cash register.
- Sales leader with high levels of responsibility for store safety, maintenance, sales record and customer relations.
- High track record for sales and great feedback from customers

## Volunteering

- Chairwomen for Annual Calgary speech tournament
- Dancer representing Chinese Calgary float on 2010 Calgary Stampede Parade. Winning Best Cultural and Best Overall Parade.
- Rowdies Member for Student Union and Husky committee organizing and executing various school events.

#### **Tutoring**

 Tutor in Western Canada High school for grade 10-12 courses ex) Physics 20, Chemistry 20-IB Math 20-1 and Math 30-1

## **Youth Mentorship Program**

 Mentor of the Youth mentorship program organized by CIWA (Calgary Immigrant Women's Association)

## **Youth Standing Committee**

 Member of the Youth Standing Committee organized by CIWA focusing on youth leadership in Calgary community.

#### Volunteer at the YWCA Childcare Centre

- volunteer at the YWCA Childcare Centre at BowValley college
- Demonstrated high level of patience, responsibility, creativity skills
- Developed high adaptability skills working with young children and toddlers.

#### EXTRA-CURRICULAR EXPERIENCE AND ACHIEVEMENTS

- Pre-Business Student Network at Western University
- UNICEF member and club representer at Western University
- Member of the Marketing Team at Western Ventures Association
- PBSN mentorship program
- Grade 9 Piano Certificate with Honours and Advance theory certificate
- Ballet (Annual performance at Jack Singer Hall)